Tufts College Graduate UP002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts College Graduate
1903 -- 1926
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Alumni Association
UP002
12 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Custodial History
The first publication on campus specifically directed at alumni, the "Tufts College Graduate" began publication in 1903 and ceased publication in 1926, when it was replaced by the "Tufts Alumni Bulletin."
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of bound volumes of the "Tufts College Graduate," from 1903 to 1926. Something of a post-graduate continuation of the literary magazine "Tuftonian," the Graduate contained essays, speeches, and poetry by Tufts alumni. The magazine also included reviews of books written by alumni. Only a small part of the publication was devoted to alumni news. As time went on, the Graduate began printing accounts of alumni events and meetings, as well as news of events occurring on campus. Additional unbound copies available in the reading room.
Related Materials
UP010, Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, DCA
- Tufts College Graduate, 1903 -- 1926; UP002.001; 12 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of bound volumes of the "Tufts College Graduate" from 1903 to 1926. Something of a post-graduate continuation of the literary magazine "Tuftonian," the Graduate contained essays, speeches, and poetry by Tufts alumni. The magazine also included reviews of books written by alumni. Only a small part of the publication was devoted to alumni news. As time went on, the Graduate began printing accounts of alumni events and meetings, as well as news of events occuring on campus. The first publication on campus specifically directed at alumni, the "Tufts College Graduate" began publication in 1903 and ceased publication in 1926, when it was replaced by the "Tufts Alumni Bulletin."
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1903-04; UP002.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1903-07; UP002.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1903-10; UP002.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1904-01; UP002.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
    Proposed alumni professorship bu Frederick W. Hamilton, pg 17-18; Proposed alumni proffesorship [Frederick W. Hamilton A1880]
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1904-04; UP002.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1904-07; UP002.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1904-10; UP002.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1905-01; UP002.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1905-04; UP002.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
    Alumni association
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1905-07; UP002.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1905-10; UP002.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1906-01; UP002.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1906-04; UP002.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1906-07; UP002.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1906-10; UP002.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
    Stephen Edward Abbott (1900). Death of, November 25,1905.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1907-01; UP002.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
    Stephen Edward Abbott (1900). Death of, November 25,1905; Alumni trustees
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1907-04; UP002.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
    Dr. John Coleman Adams (1870). An Honorable Youth (review of). [All Around Club] Luncheon, 4/13/07.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1907-07; UP002.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
    [Alumni] Eight young lawyers, biographical sketches [includes portraits]; Alumni association
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1907-10; UP002.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1908-01; UP002.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni association meetings; George Ahern (Librarian). University Club of Manila. Rev. Dr. John Coleman Adams. The Sunday School Helper (review of).John Coleman Adams (1870). Warren, Minton 1870 (obituary).
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1908-04; UP002.001.003.00005 (Box Volume 3)
    Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1908-07; UP002.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1908-10; UP002.001.003.00007 (Box Volume 3)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1909-01; UP002.001.003.00008 (Box Volume 3)
    Death of Charles Ellsworth Adams (1865), October 2, 1896. p. 190; Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1909-04; UP002.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
    [Alumni] Who's who in New England, 144 Tufts men named, p33; Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1909-07; UP002.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1909-10; UP002.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
    Alumni field day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1910-01; UP002.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1910-04; UP002.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1910-07; UP002.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
    Alumni association meetings; Alumni field day, second annual
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1910-10; UP002.001.004.00007 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1911-01; UP002.001.004.00008 (Box Volume 4)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1911-04; UP002.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
    Alumni trustees by Charles Neal Barney; Alumni field day; History of Tufts College alumni association by Joseph H. Saunfers, M.D.[includes constitution of the association of the alumni of tufts college]
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1911-07; UP002.001.005.00002 (Box Volume 5)
    Alumni association revised constitution; Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1911-10; UP002.001.005.00003 (Box Volume 5)
    Alumni association meetings; Alumni field day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1912-01; UP002.001.005.00004 (Box Volume 5)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1912-04; UP002.001.005.00005 (Box Volume 5)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1912-07; UP002.001.005.00006 (Box Volume 5)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1912-10; UP002.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1913-01; UP002.001.006.00002 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1913-04; UP002.001.006.00003 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1913-07; UP002.001.006.00004 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1913-10; UP002.001.006.00005 (Box Volume 6)
    Alumni association meetings; Henry T. Claus [A1905] about Tufts publicity.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1914-01; UP002.001.006.00006 (Box Volume 6)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1914-04; UP002.001.006.00007 (Box Volume 6)
    Alumni association meetings; Various alumni organizations arrange for banquet and grand reunion, March 7, 1914, p163; [Alumni and Faculty] Reunion Banquet, March 17, 1914 (Incl. cartoon from "Boston Post"), p. 162-165.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1914-07; UP002.001.006.00008 (Box Volume 6)
    [Alumni association] H.W. Whittemore from the ex-seceretary; Alumni association meetings; Alumni day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1914-10; UP002.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Winter, 1915; UP002.001.007.00002 (Box Volume 7)
    [Alumni association] J.H. Rorty post-impressions of Fletcher meeting
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Spring, 1915; UP002.001.007.00003 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Autumn, 1915; UP002.001.007.00004 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Winter, 1916; UP002.001.007.00005 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Spring, 1916; UP002.001.007.00006 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Summer, 1916; UP002.001.007.00007 (Box Volume 7)
    H.W. Whitmore, Alumni field day; Alumni association meetings; John Alden Adams (1910). Obituary (Death, March 9, 1916). pp. 306-07. John Coleman Adams (1870). Phi Beta Kappa - Poem, 1916. The Open Road.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Autumn, 1916; UP002.001.007.00008 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Winter, 1916; UP002.001.007.00009 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Spring, 1917; UP002.001.007.00010 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Summer, 1917; UP002.001.007.00011 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, Autumn, 1917; UP002.001.007.00012 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1917-12 -- 1918-02; UP002.001.007.00013 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1918-03 -- 1918-05; UP002.001.007.00014 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1918-06 -- 1918-08; UP002.001.007.00015 (Box Volume 7)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1918-09 -- 1918-11; UP002.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1918-12 -- 1919-02; UP002.001.008.00002 (Box Volume 8)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1919-03 -- 1919-05; UP002.001.008.00003 (Box Volume 8)
    Alumni trustees; J. C. Adams (1870). Allies of the Lord- poem; Alumni association meetings; [alumni association] Plans for more efficient administration of athletic and alumni affairs at Tufts
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1919-06 -- 1919-08; UP002.001.008.00004 (Box Volume 8)
    Alumni trustees; Alumni association meetings; Death of (1/31/19) Windom A. Allen (1915) in service (Hero Sons of Tufts) (Makes 16th gold star for Tufts).
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1919-09 -- 1919-11; UP002.001.008.00005 (Box Volume 8)
    [Alumni association] E.D. Sabine [A1896] Appointment of C.P. Houston as Graduate Manager
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1919-12 -- 1920-02; UP002.001.008.00006 (Box Volume 8)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1920-03 -- 1920-05; UP002.001.008.00007 (Box Volume 8)
    Alumni field day; Alumni association meetings; Tufts men in the Massachusetts general court [Seth F. Arnold, M1908; Richard B. Coolidge 1902; Reverend William F. Dusseault 1883; Edward Carroll Hinckley B1888; Samuel W. Mendum 1885]
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1920-06 -- 1920-08; UP002.001.008.00008 (Box Volume 8)
    Alumni day; Alumni association meetings; [Alumni] Golf Tournament [vol19, no2], pg86; Alumni association meetings; [Alumni association] E.D. Sabine [A1896] address
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1920-09 -- 1920-11; UP002.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9)
    Academic Honors, 1920-1924, p. 25. Richard C. Allen (1910) Married 11/4/20) to Grace Barber Leonard (Simmons 1911) at Newton, MA.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1920-12 -- 1921-02; UP002.001.009.00002 (Box Volume 9)
    Alumni association meetings; [Alumnae] Banquet held Dec. 31, 1920 at Hotel Bellevue, Boston; Alumni field day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1921-03 -- 1921-05; UP002.001.009.00003 (Box Volume 9)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1921-06 -- 1921-08; UP002.001.009.00004 (Box Volume 9)
    Alumni field day; [Allen, Willis Boyd] The Promised Land- Poem; Phi Beta Kappa- 5/12/21; [Alumni] Commencement activities
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1921-09 -- 1921-11; UP002.001.009.00005 (Box Volume 9)
    W. J. Alcott (1922) Professional Societies in Engineering School.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1921-12 -- 1922-02; UP002.001.009.00006 (Box Volume 9)
    Alumni association meetings [J. Porter Russell]; Alumni field day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1922-03 -- 1922-05; UP002.001.009.00007 (Box Volume 9)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1922-06 -- 1922-08; UP002.001.009.00008 (Box Volume 9)
    Alumni field day; John Coleman Adams. Death of, June 22, 1922. Death of (6/18/21) John Foster Allen (1884); [J. Porter Russell] Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1922-09 -- 1922-11; UP002.001.010.00001 (Box Volume 10)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1922-12 -- 1923-02; UP002.001.010.00002 (Box Volume 10)
    Alumni association meetings; Academic Honors, 1920-1924, p. 113. John Erwin Allen (1922) Married 1922 to Ruth Ione Marsten at North Lexington, Mass.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1923-03 -- 1923-05; UP002.001.010.00003 (Box Volume 10)
    Alumni field day; Lloyd E. Aldrich (1915) Married 3/29/23 to Marion M. Kidd at Rutland, VT; Alumni association meetings
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1923-06 -- 1923-08; UP002.001.010.00004 (Box Volume 10)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1923-09 -- 1923-11; UP002.001.011.00001 (Box Volume 11)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1923-12 -- 1924-02; UP002.001.011.00002 (Box Volume 11)
    Alumni association meetings; Academic Honors, 1920-1924, p. 104. William J. Alcott (1922) Married 9/22/23 to Mary Hazel Sproat at Everett, MA.
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1924-03 -- 1924-05; UP002.001.011.00003 (Box Volume 11)
    Charles Rollin Allen Jr. (E99) Biographical; Alumni association meetings; Alumni field day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1924-06 -- 1924-08; UP002.001.011.00004 (Box Volume 11)
    Tufts college graduate; Alumni field day; Alumni association meetings; Complete ownership of AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation]] acquired by Power, Harold J. as of July 1, 1924. p. 247
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1924-09 -- 1924-11; UP002.001.012.00001 (Box Volume 12)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1924-12 -- 1925-02; UP002.001.012.00002 (Box Volume 12)
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1925-03 -- 1925-05; UP002.001.012.00003 (Box Volume 12)
    Alumni field day; Alumni day; [Alumnae association of New York] Luncheon to discuss plans to form a New York Tufts Alumnae Association, held May 9, 1925
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1925-06 -- 1925-08; UP002.001.012.00004 (Box Volume 12)
    Alumni day
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1925-09 -- 1925-11; UP002.001.012.00005 (Box Volume 12)
    [Alumnae association of New York] Luncheon to discuss plans to form a New York Tufts Alumnae Association, held May 9, 1925
  - The Tufts College Graduate, 1925-12 -- 1926-02; UP002.001.012.00006 (Box Volume 12)
    [Alumnae] jackson night, Friday January 15, 1926